var qBank = [{
    question:"Leeds, United Kingdom is the birthplace of what Borussen?",
    answers: ["Marwin Hitz", "Jadon Sancho", "Manuel Akanji", "Erling Braut Haaland"],
    correct: "Erling Braut Haaland",
    questionId: "000001"
  },
  {
    question:'Dan-Axel Zagadou was born in',
    answers: ["Braga, Protugal", "Paris, France", "Créteil, France", "Le Blanc-Mesnil, France"],
    correct: "Créteil, France",
    questionId: "000002"
  },
  {
    question:"With 127 goals, this player is 7th on Dortmund's all-time top 10 goalscorers",
    answers: ["Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang", "Marco Reus", "Jürgen Schütz", "Lothar Emmerich"],
    correct: "Marco Reus",
    questionId: "000003"
  },
  {
    question: "Nuri Sahin became the Bundesliga's youngest scorer at what age?",
    answers: ["16 years & 238 days","17 years & 82 days","16 years & 334 days","17 years & 37 days"],
    correct: "17 years & 82 days",
    questionId: "000004"
  },
  {
    question: "What year did the Westfalenstadion open?",
    answers: ["1972","1978","1974","1975"],
    correct: "1974",
    questionId: "000005"
  },
  {
    question: "Ewerthon scored the goal to give Borussia Dortmund the lead over Bremen after only being on for _____.",
  answers: ["1 minute 4 seconds","49 seconds","1 minute 23 seconds","38 seconds"],
  correct: "49 seconds",
    questionId: "000006"
  },
  {
    question: "Borussia Dortmund finished at the top of the table with ____ in the 11/12 season.",
  answers: ["81 points","75 points","78 points","80 points"],
  correct: "81 points",
    questionId: "000007"
  },
  {
    question: "Cruising to a 4-1 victory, beating which team in the final of the 1988-89 DFB-Pokal?",
    answers: ["VfB Stuttgart", "FC Bayern", "Werder Bremen", "Bayer 04"],
    correct: "Werder Bremen",
    questionId: "000008"
  },
  {
    question:"After how many years did Borussia Dortmund get their first win against Sch*lke?",
    answers: ["18", "3", "7", "23"],
    correct: "18",
    questionId: "000009"
  },
  {
    question:"With 10 goals this player is the top time scorer in the Revierderby?",
    answers: ["Ingo Anderbrügge","Michael Zorc","Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang","Lothar Emmerich"],
    correct: "Lothar Emmerich",
    questionId: "000010"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player is a noted Dragon Ball fan?",
    answers: ["Hakimi", "Zaga", "Sancho", "Dahoud"],
    correct: "Zaga",
    questionId: "000011"
  },
  {
    question: "This player is red-green colorblind?",
    answers: ["Julian Brandt", "Roman Bürki", "Thomas Delaney", "Marco Reus"],
    correct: "Thomas Delaney",
    questionId: "000012"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was not apart of the 10/11 champion team",
    answers: ["Ilkay Gündogan", "Lukasz Piszczek", "Mario Götze", "Mitchell Langerak"],
    correct: "Ilkay Gündogan",
    questionId: "000013"
  },
  {
    question: "Which player was not in the 94/95 champion team?",
    answers: ["Andreas Möller", "Stefan Klos", "Matthias Sammer", "Marco Kurz"],
    correct: "Marco Kurz",
    questionId: "000014"
  },
  {
    question: "Lucien Favre was born in",
    answers: ["Wiesendangen, Switzerland", "Saint-Barthelemy, Switzerland", "Münsingen, Switzerland", "St. Gallen, Switzerland"],
    correct: "Saint-Barthélemy, Switzerland",
    questionId: "000015"
  },
  {
    question: "Lucien Favre became the first ever manager to remain unbeaten for how many Bundesliga matches",
    answers: ["10", "20", "15", "18"],
    correct: "15",
    questionId: "000016"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the capacity of the Westfalenstadion?",
    answers: ["81365", "81455", "81220", "81565"],
    correct: "81365",
    questionId: "000017"
  },
  {
    question:"Borussia Dortmund returned to the Bundesliga in?",
    answers: ["1973", "1975", "1976", "1978"],
    correct: "1976",
    questionId: "000018"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which company has not been a supplier of Dortmund kits?",
    answers: ["Adidas", "Nike", "Kappa", "Umbro"],
    correct: "Umbro",
    questionId: "000019"
  },
  {
    question: "Błaszczykowski was plagued by a torn leg muscle in which season?",
    answers: ["2008-09","2009-10","2010-11","2012-13"],
    correct: "2008-09",
    questionId: "000020"
  },
  {
    question: "On 1 August 2016 Błaszczykowski joined Wolfsburg for?",
    answers: ["€4 million ", "€8 million", "€5 million", "€12 million"],
    correct: "€5 million",
    questionId: "000021"
  },
  {
    question: "Shinji Kagawa initially joined Borussia Dortmund for?",
    answers: ["€3.5 million", "€350,000", "€700,000", "€5 million"],
    correct: "€350,000",
    questionId: "000022"
  },
  {
    question: "Christian Pulisic joined Chelsea in 2019 for a fee of?",
    answers: ["€64 million","€50 million","€46 million","€75 million"],
    correct: "€64 million",
    questionId: "000023"
  },
  {
    question:"When is Marco Reus' birthday?",
    answers: ["October 31", "July 6", "February 29", "May 31"],
    correct: "May 31",
    questionId: "000024"
  },
  {
    question: "Which manager signed Guerreiro?",
    answers: ["Tuchel", "Stöger", "Favre", "Bosz"],
    correct: "Tuchel",
    questionId: "000025"
  },
  {
    question: "How fast did Erling Haaland score a hattrick on his debut?",
    answers: ["45 minutes", "23 minutes", "36 minutes", "12 minutes"],
    correct: "23 minutes",
    questionId: "000026"
  },
  {
    question: "How many appearances did Matthias Sammer make for Borussia Dortmund?",
    answers: ["115", "75", "200", "25"],
    correct: "115",
    questionId: "000027"
  },
  {
    question: "Which manager led Dortmund to their title in 2002?",
    answers: ["Udo Lattek", "Matthias Sammer", "Lucien Favre", "Bert van Marwijk"],
    correct: "Matthias Sammer",
    questionId: "000028"
  },
  {
    question: "What is Mats Hummels middle name?",
    answers: ["Jakob", "Mats", "Julian", "Martin"],
    correct: "Julian",
    questionId: '000029'
  },
  {
    question: "How many goals did Jadon Sancho score in the 2018-19 season?",
    answers: ["10", "16", "14", "12"],
    correct: "12",
    questionId: "000030"
  },
  {
    question: 'When did Gio Reyna make is BVB debut?',
    answers: ["February 4, 2020","January 24, 2020","January 18, 2020","February 5, 2020"],
    correct:"January 18, 2020",
    questionId: "000031" 
  },
  {
    question:"Which year was the Revierderby born?",
    answers: ["1925", "1909", "1927", "1918"],
    correct: "1925",
    questionId: "000032"
  },
  {
    question: "When did Borussia Dortmund begin wearing black and yellow",
    answers: ["1963","1909","1925","1913"],
    correct: "1913",
    questionId: "000033"
  },
  {
    question:"In the 2012-13 season, how many goals did Robert Lewandowski score?",
    answers: ["20", "24", "26", "17"], 
    correct: "24",
    questionId: "000034"
  },
  {
    question: "Emre Can was born in which German city?",
    answers: ["Munich","Berlin","Frankfurt am Main","Leipzig"],
    correct: "Frankfurt am Main",
    questionId: "000035"
  },
  {
    question: "Which team has Emre Can not played for?",
    answers: ["Manchester United","Bayer Leverkusen","Bayern Munich","Juventus"],
    correct: "Manchester United",
    questionId: "000036"
  },
  {
    question: "With which club did Jadon Sancho begin his career?",
    answers: ["Manchester City","Arsenal","Southampton","Watford"],
    correct: "Watford",
    questionId: "000037"
  },
  {
    question: "Which Dortmunder was not in the 2014 WC German squad?",
    answers: ["Kevin Grosskreutz","Erik Durm","Marco Reus","Mats Hummels"],
    correct: "Marco Reus",
    questionId: "000038"
  },
  {
    question: "In 2016-17 Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang was the Bundesliga leading scorer with how many goals?",
    answers: ["29","31","32","27"],
    correct: "31",
    questionId: "000039"
  },
  {
    question: "Borussia Dortmund won the 2016-17 DFB-Pokal with what score?",
    answers: ["1-0","2-0","2-1","3-2"],
    correct: "2-1",
    questionId: "000040"
  },
  {
    question: "Erling Haalands initial contract with BVB is set to end in what year?",
    answers: ["2022","2023","2024","2025"],
    correct: "2024",
    questionId: "000041"
  },
  {
    question: "How tall is Dan-Axel Zagadou?",
    answers: ["190 cm","196 cm","198 cm","189 cm"],
    correct: "196 cm",
    questionId: "000042"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the original colors of BVB?",
    answers: ["Blue & White","Red & Blue","Black & Yellow","Green & Black"],
    correct: "Blue & White",
    questionId: "000043"
  },
  {
    question: "Who wore the captain's armband the longest?",
    answers: ["Lothar Huber","Michael Zorc","Marcel Schmelzer","Sebastian Kehl"],
    correct: "Michael Zorc",
    questionId: "000044"
  },
  {
    question: "Borussia Dortmund suffered the biggest defeat in the Bundesliga with what scoreline?",
    answers: ["9-0","12-0","20-2","12-1"],
    correct: "12-0",
    questionId: "000045"
  },
  {
    question: "In which season were Dortmund not Bundesliga champions?",
    answers: ["1965-66","1995-96","1961-62","2010-11"],
    correct: "1965-66",
    questionId: "000046"
  },
  {
    question: "How many times have Dortmund wont the DFB-Pokal?",
    answers: ["7 times"," 4 times","3 times","2 times"],
    correct: "4 times",
    questionId: "000047"
  },
  {
    question: "When did Watzke become CEO",
    answers: ["February 2005"," December 2004","July 2004","July 2005"],
    correct: "February 2005",
    questionId: "000048"
  },
  {
    question: "Stadion Rote Erde was the first team stadium until when?",
    answers: ["1974","1976","1995","1982"],
    correct: "1974",
    questionId: "000049"
  },
  {
    question: "How many appearances did Roman Weidenfeller make for BVB?",
    answers: ["355","350","349","301"],
    correct: "349",
    questionId: "000050"
  },
  {
    question: "Borussia Dortmund acquired İlkay Gündoğan from which club?",
    answers: ["Sch*lke","VfL Bochum","1. FC Nürnberg","Werder Bremen"],
    correct: "1. FC Nürnberg",
    questionId: "000051"
  },
  {
    question: "What number does Julian Brandt wear?",
    answers: ["18","19","5","11"],
    correct: "19",
    questionId: "000052"
  },
];

export default qBank;